question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons respect William Shakespeare, they even suspect him having a Klingon lineage.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are commonly referred to as &quot;Black Elves&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Star Trek: The Next Generation&quot;, Data is the only android in existence.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An episode of &quot;The Simpsons&quot; is dedicated to Moe Szyslak&#039;s bar rag.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;The Simpsons&quot; family is named after creator Matt Groening&#039;s real family.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
